# dictionary used to store the possible questions and their choices
test_dict = {
            "question1": {
                "question": "this is question 1",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 1 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 1 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 1 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 1 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 1 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question2": {
                "question": "this is question 2",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 2 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 2 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 2 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 2 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 2 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question3": {
                "question": "this is question 3",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 3 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 3 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 3 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 3 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 3 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question4": {
                "question": "this is question 4",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 4 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 4 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 4 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 4 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 4 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question5": {
                "question": "this is question 5",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 5 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 5 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 5 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 5 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 5 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question6": {
                "question": "this is question 6",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 6 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 6 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 6 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 6 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 6 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question7": {
                "question": "this is question 7",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 7 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 7 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 7 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 7 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 7 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question8": {
                "question": "this is question 8",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 8 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 8 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 8 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 8 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 8 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question9": {
                "question": "this is question 9",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 9 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 9 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 9 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 9 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 9 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question10": {
                "question": "this is question 10",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 10 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 10 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 10 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 10 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 10 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question11": {
                "question": "this is question 11",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 11 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 11 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 11 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 11 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 11 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question12": {
                "question": "this is question 12",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 12 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 12 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 12 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 12 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 12 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question13": {
                "question": "this is question 13",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 13 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 13 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 13 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 13 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 13 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question14": {
                "question": "this is question 14",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 14 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 14 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 14 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 14 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 14 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question15": {
                "question": "this is question 15",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 15 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 15 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 15 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 15 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 15 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question16": {
                "question": "this is question 16",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 16 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 16 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 16 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 16 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 16 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question17": {
                "question": "this is question 17",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 17 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 17 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 17 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 17 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 17 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question18": {
                "question": "this is question 18",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 18 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 18 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 18 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 18 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 18 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question19": {
                "question": "this is question 19",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 19 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 19 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 19 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 19 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 19 wrong choice 4"
                }
            },
            "question20": {
                "question": "this is question 20",
                "choices": {
                    "answer": "this is question 20 answer",
                    "wrong1": "this is question 20 wrong choice 1",
                    "wrong2": "this is question 20 wrong choice 2",
                    "wrong3": "this is question 20 wrong choice 3",
                    "wrong4": "this is question 20 wrong choice 4"
                }
            }
}
